[Music]
hey guys real quick I just wanted to
tell you about our sponsor threat Locker
now wait wait before you hit the skip
forward button let me just say this most
of the stuff that holds my attention
nowadays is red team stuff as well but I
sat down with the threat Locker team
this past week to do a demo of their EDR
software and it was super technically
fascinating how this thing works so
check this out you drop this thing on a
system right and for the first week or
so it's creating a policy and a profile
for that system it's logging all the
executables uh what child processes are
being spawned uh the files and their
hashes that sort of thing and it's
creating this policy okay then after the
learning mode is up we're in sec mode
and that policy gets put into place and
anything that's not on that allow list
is immediately autod denied that's the
zero trust piece right so in addition to
that they've got a bunch of crazy
features like ring fencing and dynamic
access controls that would stop a
malicious hacker at pretty much every
step along the way actually I I was
watching this demo and I was kind of
freaked out because I have no idea how I
would cope with getting dropped into a
threat locker system as a red teamer
anyway if you want to learn more about
this head over to threat locker.com and
request a demo and and when you do ask
for my boy Andrew his demo was super to
the point and he was able to answer all
my technical questions all right cool
back to the show yo yo yo what's going
on everybody this is techno geek uh Joel
we're doing a solo episode today um so
this one is going to be all focused on
part-time bug Bounty um you know as
Justin is a full-time bug Bounty Hunter
but I am a parttime bug Bounty Hunter
and uh this was a requested episode from
um some of the listeners um within the
our Discord server so I wanted to take
some time to talk about some strategies
and some different aspects of the
part-time uh bug Bounty hacking life so
to speak um I'm a lot more versed on
that than I than Justin is I think so I
it's definitely a unique perspective and
I wanted to just share some of my
thoughts share some of my strategies
share some of the tips and tricks and
all that sort of good stuff uh all
around that but first I wanted to talk
about some news uh so I I know the last
few episodes have been interviews so um
I don't know if there's been too much
news but there were two main things that
I want to talk about um that had come up
in the last couple weeks um the first
one was a really cool post by uh retr
regge with a zero uh on zero. dev that's
that's their blog um Patrick Pang um and
this blog post was all about an Evernote
bug that they found that was it started
as a font injection basically JavaScript
injection into uh
pdf.js within the Evernote um desktop
application and they were able to
escalate that all the way up to remote
code execution so it's a really really
awesome blog post um it's very in- depth
it talks about sort of the whole
strategy the whole mindset the the whole
you know behind the scenes of what went
into finding the bug and how they were
able to locate this um basically what
they were able to do is they they found
that ever know uses pdf. J s which is
very large very well-known JavaScript
library for um rendering PDFs
and within this there's this font um
this font you know construct or whatever
I'm not sure what the right word is
directive I guess um and you can create
these font objects and the way that it's
parsed by pdf.js is faulty and you can
use this to basically sync all the way
into a function creation call within the
JavaScript that creates a new JavaScript
function to get arbitrary JavaScript
execution so from there you have
JavaScript execution when a PDF gets
loaded and rendered by pdf.js within the
Evernote app but due to the restrictions
that were in place for security purposes
you couldn't steal their cookies you
couldn't you know take over the account
very easily you couldn't do do much at
that point but there is this
interprocess communication um you know
functionality that's built into these
electron apps that allows um apps to
talk with different part different other
parts of the app um you know there's
like Bridges and there's you know sort
of sectioned off parts of the
application that are communicated
through this IPC process and through
this there was a specific IPC Handler
called like the broker Bridge um where
you could do all these different actions
and one of those actions ended up being
that you could open file attachments um
and so through this very elaborate
payload which uh is if you read through
it you're like what the heck is this um
but he he does a great job of sort of
breaking down all the different parts
and what each part means and how it
works and and so on um and it basically
allows you to put through a file path
like calc.exe that will you fully
execute and open on the uh on the on the
victim when the PDF gets rendered and
opened by the Evernote application so
it's a really really awesome blog post
very very cool um great research uh
really does a great job of demonstrating
how you can sort of take that to the
next level because I think you probably
could have
just submitted it as his and said hey
you know I have this vulnerability I can
execute JavaScript within the PDF when
it loads done you know maybe it's a
medium maybe it's a high or something
and just call it a day but um he really
pushed through went the extra mile and
found that that impact there and uh and
got it all the way to uh remote code
execution code execution pile execution
not really sure which which one it would
be I
guess not really RC but file execution
remote file execution RF
anyways um yeah so very cool check out
that blog post read read through it um I
know a lot of electron apps are out
there it's a very interesting attack
surface if you ask me because it's sort
of that bridge between um where xss
starts to affect client applications
there's a ton of electron apps out there
I think a really famous example is um
Discord uh I don't know if it's still
fully electron but it's JavaScript based
um and you know it basically is has a
console and everything so um yeah
there's there's definitely a lot of
applications out there that are using
JavaScript and are using electron and
it's probably a probably a ripe attack
service for some vulnerabilities um cool
the next bug blog post I wanted to talk
about was from AET node as always the
folks over at asset node are doing crazy
crazy awesome research um and this one
was a very elaborate bug chain in
service now um that let them escalate to
um being able to access basically all of
your service now data um so it started
out that they were they noticed that
there was this strange decoding Behavior
where uh there's sort of two levels of
um protection on this rendering there's
there's this template renderer um and if
you can manage to get some tags through
this template rendering process then and
you would have you know potentially very
serious implications uh through full
template injection and so they started
looking through the service Now
application and they found a specific
spot where there uh there's no escaping
explicitly being done on user input um
and they were able to find a way to get
a a user controlled parameter that just
dumps directly into the page and they
started fiddling around with it so um
ASD note does a really awesome job of
sort of walking through their thought
process as well of you know this is what
we tried this didn't work then we looked
here oh we noticed this interesting
thing then we tried that that didn't
work oh we noticed another thing and so
on so it's a very very good read it's
very easy very digestible but it's it's
an awesome demonstration of how you can
escalate a bug so they went back in
Forth basically with the application
they notice okay there's a sanitizer
here oh we can only put certain tags
through all right style tag is allowed
we use a style tag to escape the HTML
now we can put arbitrary tags in okay
now how do we actually get this to do
what we want we want to use this
evaluate tag so that we can actually run
our own code uh in the template exec in
the template uh rendering engine right
but you can only use these certain types
of tags so they try you know defining
their own tag they try changing the Nam
space there's a specific check for that
they can't define the Nam space um then
they try overriding the default
namespace uh and then there's another
check on that they go and they look how
does that check work oh the check works
with the
Rex is the Rex satisfactory no you can
bypass it with single quotes instead of
double double quotes and so and so on
and so on so it's a really really
awesome bug um it's it's super super
cool that shows again sort of this
thought process of um you know sort of
one step at a time getting past these
security controls testing iterating
figuring out how to continue to escalate
this further and further and further
until you get to sort of your maximum
Ino impact uh point and um yeah it's a
really really awesome bug um at the end
of the day they were able to get you
know arbitrary file read essentially on
the server so they could read um you
know user uh data they could read um the
config files for the server they could
also on a lot of instances I guess
there's this uh cross uh server
communication thing so similar kind of
like an IPC but it's not inner process
it's like inner node um and it basically
is just rce as a service so you can just
run commands you can run curl and just
have it you know run whatever you want
um that worked uh evidently it seems so
there was a lot of really interesting
stuff that they were able to do um and
since they have sort of this evaluate
context where they're within um the
template engine they have access to
different classes and and all sorts of
very complex sort of attack vectors uh
that are that are now available to them
because they're within like sort of java
Java execution context so it's a very
very interesting blog post definitely go
check it out it's on the asset note uh
website and yeah um last thing I'd be
remiss if I didn't mention this
obviously crowd strike stuff I don't
really have much to say about this from
a bug Bounty perspective uh that it
wasn't really bug Bounty related it's
just some crazy uh crazy security stuff
that came up uh in the last couple weeks
um for those of you who don't know there
was a crowd strike um they pushed I
guess a a bug or something in one of in
the crowd strike agent on Windows and it
was causing blue screens it created huge
outages all around uh the world all
around tons of Industries I believe
there were many airlines who were down
who were down for like many many days I
think Delta might still be dealing with
problems um but yeah obviously um just
goes to sort of show how stuff can
Cascade right and and what the impacts
of very small bugs even not necessarily
a security bug but just a bug in general
uh can have so just uh just some food
for thought hey guys real quick I just
wanted to give a shout to the hacker
content team they have been absolutely
killing it the past couple months taking
the content from the podcast and
condensing it down into consumable
social media posts whether it be shorts
or text posts or whatever they've been
rocking it so uh I just wanted to give
them a shout out and let you know that
they do all sorts of cybercity content
as well as social media management they
do technical blogs they do uh
comprehensive social media management uh
so if your organization could benefit
from any of those types of services make
sure you head over to hacker content.com
drop them a line and mention the podcast
when you do to get your first month of
cyber security content marketing
services for free all right that's it
let's get back to the Pod uh all right
let's get into the main content for
today which is parttime bug bny all
right so as I mentioned I am a part-time
book b Hunter um that is you know my
main focus um I
uh I work fulltime um and I have like a
million other side things that I do all
the time including this
podcast um and so I think for a lot of
people it can be very daunting to figure
out sort of the time management aspects
especially and so I just wanted to cover
like sort of a couple different topics
around part-time bug money and and the
first one is how to balance your time um
between like hacking and family and um
work and life and not going insane and
all that kind of stuff right so I I
think the first thing that you really
have to do is you have to choose how
serious you want to take this um you
know bug
Bounty can be a very lucrative way to
make a lot of money it can also be just
like a very normal side hustle maybe you
make you know 100 bucks a month 500
bucks a month um you know it really it
is what you make of it and you can be
very successful or you can take it very
casually um I think especially when
you're doing it parttime it's really
important to remember you're doing a lot
already okay so for whatever your
reasons are whether you're in school
whether you're um you're employed
full-time whether you have kids whether
you're working two jobs like whatever it
is like you've probably already got a
lot going on if bug bounding something
that you're aiming to do part-time um
and so it's important to just to
recognize that right um if you're going
to go really hard on this you're going
to go intense you're going to go all in
then set some strict schedules you know
give yourself um you know you say I'm G
to hack two three hours a day five hours
a day whatever you know from this time
to this time and you put that on your
calendar and you block it out and you
say sorry I'm busy I I have something
going on I have an appointment you know
um you just need to be dedicated and be
explicit and be um intentional about
your time when you're if you're going to
be ser about
it um along with that like you need to
commit to what your schedule is right so
if you're saying that you're going to
work for two hours a day from you know 7
to 9
p.m. then at 7 pm you drop what you're
doing and you go if somebody says hey
can you uh are you free at 7:30 n sorry
I've got something going on right you
you have to commit to that and you need
to hold yourself accountable accountable
and you need to build accountability
into it right so whether that's tracking
your time whether that's having a buddy
to hack with whether that's having
someone who you say yeah I hacked today
no I didn't hack today um you know build
accountability into your process so that
you can hold yourself accountable and
you can be honest with yourself right um
if you're going to track your time
there's a couple really easy ways to do
that um you can do it through there's a
great application I like called clockify
which basically you can just set
projects and you it's just a desktop app
and you click Start stop you say I'm
working on this and it tracks your time
um you can view all your stats it syncs
online it's free easy it's great um if
you don't want to do that you can just
use a timer on your phone um you can uh
track it in a Google sheet um I've done
that as well actually this year is a new
thing for me I've been tracking all of
my time spent hacking I've tracking how
many bugs I submit um bounties that I
earn every single day of the year um
just so that you know have those numbers
and if you're not hacking you put a zero
in there all right that's how it works
that's called being honest you got to be
honest with yourself with yourself if
you're going to take this seriously uh
which I think you should um regardless
of how intense you take it you need to
be honest with yourself how much time
are you actually spending how much time
how many bugs are you actually
submitting how many bugs are actually
getting paid out and then at the end the
year if you don't like what those
numbers look like then you can try and
make some changes and you can say okay I
wanted to do this but I but I I didn't
and this is what the actual this is what
reality looked like versus what I wanted
it to look like what went wrong did I
not take it seriously enough like what
what happened there um so you know build
build an accountability track your time
track you know your your progress be
honest about that tracking with yourself
um if you need to find somebody who you
can hack with find someone to collab
with we got ton of people in our Discord
ctbb showd Discord go find some find
find a hacking partner find a hacking
buddy split 50/50 and just you know go
ham um another strategy that I love um
that France uses and I also like to use
sometimes is like using Cliffhangers um
or you can use any sort of dopamine
chasing strategy that works for you so
whether that's um you know setting
setting up you know something that's
really exciting and then stopping
hacking right before that so that the
next day you're really excited to come
and look at that thing that you were
looking at the day before um you can do
that or you know if it's changing
targets frequently what whatever works
for you um that like gives you that Rush
use that to your advantage um you have
to sort of be your own coach in this
scenario where you need to find the
strategies that work for you that allow
you to work optimally and capitalize on
those so that you are in the optimal
space to hack when you want to hack and
when you need to hack
okay next picking programs picking
programs is a big topic for part-time
hackers um because there's all sorts of
questions around you pick one target you
pick a bunch of targets you change
Target targets three times a day um do
you do you hone in and and go ham on a
single Target like what do you do so um
there's
definitely a lot of different ways to do
this I don't want to get too much into
the Weeds on like you should focus
specifically on this one program or not
if that's your hacking style that's
great um if I always recommend going
deep you know getting very intimate with
the application finding all of the
routes all of the ins and outs all the
little quirks and nuances and
abbreviations and everything about that
program so that you are as knowledgeable
as an engineer at that company when
you're hacking on that and that will
allow you to make connections and tie
things together and use those gadgets
very very effectively if you're that
comfortable with the application it's
going to be a lot harder to do that if
you're not that that's just that's what
I found right um that's not to say that
you can't find bugs without doing that
right there's tons of ways to do that
and I I'll talk a little bit about that
later um but you know that's definitely
a a good way to keep yourself um you
know focused is to go deep on an
application and and focus only on that
one application become an expert there
um so one thing that I like to do when
I'm looking for programs is optimize for
payouts um and impact um and so I
think those two things go hand inand if
you want the highest payout you want the
highest impact right so there's a script
that I wrote um it's going to be
released to the critical thinkers
hopefully before this episode if not
check the Discord but um it uh it will
be exclusive to the critical thinkers
and it basically does a bunch of program
sta
using your hacker one token your cookie
whatever off off cookie to look at all
the programs that you're on and we look
at their bounties and look at their
stats on their Bounty tables and it will
identify programs that are potentially
really good targets um and the way that
it does this is that it looks at some of
the payout statistics based on what is
the average Bounty based on their Bounty
table what is the percentage of bounties
that are within High highend crit range
how far off from the max highend crit
are the average payouts for heising
crits stuff like that so it's a very
very useful tool it definitely
identified a couple different programs
that me and uh Justin were both very
interested in so uh it works and it's
it's a it's a super useful tool uh I'm
working out some minor quirks with the
authentication problems for some reason
it works for me but it doesn't work for
other people so um I'm I'm still working
out some of the Kinks there but it's a
very useful tool um so that'll be
available to our our critical thinker
tier but um you can do that manually as
well so if you want just go to your
program dashboard your you know hacker
dashboard oror start looking through
programs and start looking at their
tables and see what percentage of
reports or highs in crits how far are
they deviating from their payout table
in terms of bounties how how hard are
they adhering to their Bounty table and
CVSs and that's going to tell you how
how easy it's going to be in terms of
poundies right when you have a program
who really strongly years to CVSs and
their Bounty table where it's a high it
gets this much it's a crit it gets this
much um that type of program is as a
part-time Hunter where you want to be
spending your time because you want to
be making the most amount of money
without fighting back and forth about
the team you if you find a high you want
that Bounty right so um that's
definitely something to keep in
mind um another thing to keep in mind is
from the impact scenario right so put
yourself in the shoes of the security
team when you are submitting a bug you
want to think about what it would be
like to be sitting at your desk as a
security team and a researcher with your
username submits a report and it just
came into your
inbox number one how does it read right
so remember that you're communicating
with a real human um and that some real
person is going to be reading that
report so how how are you speaking how
are you phrasing things is it easy to
understand is it overly complicated is
is there unnecessary details that don't
need to be in there there's a lot of
aspects to writing a good report um that
can be solved by just thinking about how
it would be by reading it from the
perspective of the security team the
other thing
is the impact assessment from the
security team so if you're in the shoes
of the security team what is your worst
case scenario what uh is it user data is
it rce is it accessing some specific
service is it being able to bypass this
certain role um what is you know what is
the worst case scenario and what are
those more or less impactful things that
you can do on that program um as you
know if you're on the security team what
would make a bug more impactful what
would make a bug less impactful what
things would be u m mitigating factors
that an attacker would need to get
around or find a way to bypass in order
to raise the impact on their bug um you
know when time is
limited when when it's scarce you have
to hyper
optimize the things that you're looking
for and you have to angle and Orient
your reports in a way such that they
highlight the highest possible impact
scenario for that program so that you
can maximize your severity you can
maximize your impact you can maximize
your payout right so on the topic of
optimizing and especially keeping your
flow
as streamlined as possible let's talk
about spending your time efficiently um
I've mentioned a couple times Impact
versus volume are you going for a lot of
reports that may be mediums or are you
going for three crits a month one crit a
month what is your goal here right um
make sure that you're setting your goals
appropriately and that you're not
switching back and forth if you're if
you have a Target and you constantly
change that Target you're never going to
be able to make progress towards that
Target because the target's always
shifting so set a Target keep that
Target and continue to focus towards it
if that Target is I want to find a crit
go until you find a crit don't go for
three hours and then say okay never mind
that's actually too hard I want to find
a medium now like that's fine but you
should set goals and you should work to
towards those goals until you achieve it
not just constantly shifted because
you're going to feel like you're
constantly stalling and it's it's going
to put you in a negative head space
um another great strategy is to follow
Douglas day's uh nose talk uh about
looking for the nose in an application
uh Douglas day AKA Archangel friend of
the show friend of he's been on the pot
a couple times uh he has a great talk
about looking for NOS in an application
which are basically things that are
explicitly called out as you shouldn't
be able to do this uh it it shouldn't be
possible to do this thing um you know
there it users should only be able to do
X Y and Z right look look at the
documentation read through um what the
application says about itself look for
permissions look for role-based
access controls um these are the types
of things that you want to try and get
around those can be really easy wins and
those can also have very strong impact
scenarios where you can say here's your
documentation that says you shouldn't be
able to do this here's me doing it very
very straightforward cut and dry usually
works very very
well um another thing for spending your
time efficiently is to map the product
and identify your whole attack surface
so the first thing that I always try and
do when I'm looking at an application is
figure out what am I dealing with what
stuff is available to me what looks
interesting where am my possible attack
scenarios what possible routes and
gadgets do I have available
what endpoint is returning what to me
where do I have user info where do I
have permissions where do I have access
control checks all sorts of things make
these notes take notes write them down
right um super super important that you
figure out just the fundamentals of the
application that you explore and you you
get Hands-On time with the application
if you're trying to hack it efficiently
and you're trying to be able to make
those connections in your brain when you
see something funny all
right um for the impact side when when I
talked about volume versus impact if
you're going to be going after
impact focus on high impact bugs okay
you have to set those targets
appropriately don't be like uh maybe
I'll find an idor that leaks user info
maybe you will and that could be a very
severe bug but that's going to depend on
the program and that's going to depend
on their impact scenario that's going to
dep depend on their risk model right so
again when you're putting yourself in
the shoes of that security team think
about what their risk model looks like
what is their threat and impact model is
it leaking user data or is it account
takeover is it access to internal
applications is there a Walled Garden
going on right so look for account
takeovers look for ssrf look for ways to
bypass parsers PDF exports um f exports
template injection
rce right there's a lot of really juicy
scenarios nowadays that aren't just all
in the browser um that are really high
impact and if you focus just on those
you're definitely going to find at least
a few of
them um and as I mentioned going going
deep um becoming super intimate with the
application again like the those couple
of hours that you spend every single day
over one week two weeks a month that
will add up to a lot of time and you
will become very very well versed with
that application and as soon as you see
a bug you're going to be able to connect
the dots in your head and you're going
to be able to to write up a bug
immediately you're G you're going to
know exactly what to do you're you're
GNA see it you're gonna go oh I have a
thing for this yeah so last thing I
wanted to talk about streamlining
streamlining your process make it
efficient um how do how do we how do we
add some grease into the system how do
we you know slow as smooth smooth smooth
is fast so F whatever how do we make
this better how do we streamline our
process okay step one just like Greece
reduce friction okay this is going to
depend person by person you need to find
where the highest friction areas are in
your process so when you're
hacking there's going to be things where
you're going to be like G this is so
annoying I hate this part uh this is
always so annoying for me it's so
frustrating that I have to do
XYZ and I'm not going to start hacking
because I have to do that or it off you
know it's off-putting right whatever
those friction points are whatever those
those negative annoyances are you need
to fix those things okay so whether
that's creating report templates because
writing reports sucks whether that's
using bash aliases and creating shell
scripts for yourself that you can
execute to do a bunch of different
commands at the same time because
remembering all that stuff is annoying
whether that's creating custom
automations and tools and scanning
Suites bind your own blockers and solve
your own blockers right this is a really
important part of your process that you
can't just let these problems live and
say well I have a limited amount of time
so uh I I just need to hack I can't go
and fix this problem no spending time
fixing a problem is not a waste of time
okay when you have a problems you
spending time fixing that is really
really important it's very important to
actually spend time fixing that problem
that is part of optimizing and part of
fixing that for every single time that
you hack after that if you have a
problem you fix it once never again it's
very you know so make sure to spend the
time to fix those things on on the other
hand don't overdo it okay it's so easy
to
just say oh I could optimize this oh let
me automate that keep it simple right
keep it simple but if it's clunky if
it's if it's a blocker if it's creating
more problems than it's solving
optimize it okay don't over complicate
it but but don't let it you know be a
blocker right
so find your own problems fix fix those
problems optimize your process next take
notes I said this at least twice during
this episode take notes take notes take
notes and and the most important part of
taking notes is reviewing your notes my
goodness I cannot tell you how many
times I've taken notes and I I just
don't even I don't even look at them I
just I'm just writing stuff down not
even looking at what I'm writing not
weeks go by I'm like wow I've taken a
lot of notes don't even read them read
your notes you took the notes for a
reason okay in your notes you should
have a lot of very useful tips for
yourself otherwise you're taking in
efficient notes so your notes should be
things that you in the future want to
look back at so look back at it okay
it's very important that's a very
important part of taking notes is
reading the notes okay record videos
record audio for yourself doesn't have
to be video you don't you go my face is
ugly I can't don't I don't want to be on
video great record a voice memo for
yourself about what you were doing at
the end of your hacking session brain
dump into either a video or an audio you
can do this for gadgets you can do it
for your whole hacking session you can
do it however you want Loom is a great
way to do this because it records your
face and your screen you can use OBS if
you don't want to use some other
software uh you can use freaking quick
time on Mac um you know there's tons of
ways to record your screen um and your
audio record to yourself you're just
talking to yourself and brain dump
because the next time that you go to
hack you can open that video you got you
know a 3 to five minute video that you
could just listen get right back into
into that headp space that you're at at
the end of your last hacking session you
can jump right back into it without
having to try and figure stuff out
again um other ways of taking notes
notion I use notion for my notes it's
great it's like kind of marked down
Niche on steroids it's really really
nice um it has a lot of awesome features
like you know collapsible sections and
tables and all whatever you there
there's a lot of stuff you can do with
notion I think there's another tool
called obsidian I want to say um that's
like more open source brain mapping type
note taking stuff there's a ton of
options out there you can use Evernote
if you want uh as we talked about
earlier I that's I'll leave that up to
the The Listener
um uh you can also use a whiteboard I
just bought a whiteboard you can't see
it it's off screen right now but I
bought a massive whiteboard for my wall
um so you can just you know write down
some notes dump stuff on there you know
map stuff out on there um sticky notes I
love Sticky Notes I have a of sticky
notes right here I keep them on my desk
I have a pencil on my desk and if uh
sometimes even in the middle of the
podcast Justin will say something and I
don't want to interrupt him or I have a
thought uh that I want to you know make
a note of or an idea that I I don't want
to leak on the podcast and uh I'll take
a sticky note and I'll write it down and
I'll just put it on my desk or I'll put
it on my monitor take
notes very good sticky notes notion
notes video notes whiteboard
notes notes very good okay that is
pretty much all I've got
um there's obviously a lot more that you
can do but I think sort of the best
advice that I have is iterate take notes
and identify the blockers in your
process right streamline what you do
when again when time is limited you have
to optimize okay if you want to be the
most efficient hacker that you can in
the amount of time that you have as a
part time hacker you have to find the
ways to make your process the best as
possible you need to figure out the way
that you want to hack whether that's
high impact whether that's high volume
whether that's focusing on one program
whether that's changing all the time and
you need to find the ways that work for
you that are successful and figure out
the goals and the things that you want
to get out of this if you want to get a
certain amount of money set that money
as a goal track it in a spreadsheet
track it in clockify track it on your
phone track it in a Notes app track it
however want to track it and hold
yourself accountable right be honest
with
yourself and it's okay to take breaks to
fix problems to let yourself recharge
and to recognize that you are doing a
lot and it's just a part-time thing
so you you know you get out what you put
in so you got this good luck part-time
hackers I believe in you I'm with there
I'm with you on there you got this good
luck see you on the
leaderboards
peace and that's a wrap on this episode
of critical thinking thanks so much for
listening and if you want more critical
thinking content head over to ctbb Dosh
show/ Discord join the Discord there's
lots of great conversations and chats
going on over there and if you want to
support the show there's the Discord
subscriber tiers which give you access
to master classes amas hack alongs
exclusive scripts and an exclusive chat
Channel with us we'll see you there